Narrator: 1
Speaker 1: Is Sydney the capital of Australia?
Speaker 2: No, it isn’t.
Narrator: 2
Speaker 1: Are you English?
Speaker 2: No, I’m not.
Narrator: 3
Speaker 1: Is Asterix French?
Speaker 2: Yes, he is.
Narrator: 4
Speaker 1: Are the Simpsons English?
Speaker 2: No, they aren’t.
Narrator: 5
Speaker 1: Is sushi Chinese?
Speaker 2: No, it isn’t.
Narrator: 6
Speaker 1: Are Zara and Mango from Italy?
Speaker 2: No, they aren’t.
Narrator: 7
Speaker 1: Is Glasgow in Scotland?
Speaker 2: Yes, it is.
Narrator: 8
Speaker 1: Are Honda and Suzuki Japanese?
Speaker 2: Yes, they are.
Narrator: 9
Speaker 1: Is JK Rowling American?
Speaker 2: No, she isn’t.
Narrator: 10
Speaker 1: Is New York the capital of the United States?
Speaker 2: No, it isn’t.